

CURRICULUM VITAE



I am a student at Primagraha University, Islamic Religious Education Undergraduate Study Program, I was born in Serang on 22 July 2001 I am ready to work hard and ready to take responsibility for what is entrusted to me. I also have expertise in photography and videography for 1.5 months, and I also like new things.



WORK EXPERIENCE

- ***** Operator School (2023-2024)
- **❖** TEACHER TAHFIDZ QUR'AN (2020-2023)



EDUCATION

- ❖ SD NEGERI KASEMEN (2012-2013)
- ***** MTS PERSIS SERANG (2015-2016)
- **SMK NEGERI 6 PRIYAI (2018-2019)**
- **❖** Pon-Pes Al-Qur'an Basyariyyah (2020-2023)



MY SKILL

- ❖ MS.WORD
- **❖** MS.EXCEL
 - CANVA
 - ***** CAPCUT



ORGANIZATION

Dewan Penggalang Pramuka (2015)

Pengawas TPS (2024)



MY CONTACT



+62 83152515210



@fjrnrfzi



Fjrnrfzi22@gmail.com



@Jar



HOBBIES







